

VAN HUNG HOANG WEB DEVELOPER & MARKETING

CONTACT INFO

- +61415539727
- Marryhung195@gmail.com
- https://harryhung195.github.io/resumevan-hung-hoang/
- https://github.com/harryhung195
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/van-hung-hoang-668049125/
- Manager Coffee Shop and Baker In WA
- 🌺 AQS Tannery Group
- 💡 Sunshine North, Vic, Australia

EDUCATION

- 2015-2017
- Study course Leadership And Project Management Practice
- Tafe in WA
- 2017-2020
- Bachelor degree in Information Technology
- University in WA

PROFILE

I am a mature, positive and hardworking individual, who always strives to achieve the highest standard possible, at any given task.

In my previous role as a Sales Representative and Web Developer, I demonstrated the ability to work under intense pressure, sell products and services to customers from all backgrounds, handle customer complaints and solve problematic situations as and when they arose. I was promoted twice for exceeding my sales targets. I am a committed, friendly and hardworking Customer Service Advisor with a passion for providing excellent customer service at all times, always having the needs of the customers and the reputation of the organization at heart. I have dealt with customers enquiries and complaints face-to-face.

My excellent customer service and communication skills, combined with my relevant work experience, make me a real asset to any organization that I work. I have excellent communication skills, enabling me to effectively communicate with a wide range of people.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- 2014-2016
- COOKIES AND DONUTS IN SOUTHLANDS, WA

WORK AT COFFEE SHOP

- customer service skills, the ability to work well with others, the ability
 to sell products and services, the ability to work on your own, excellent
 verbal communication skills, a good memory, the ability to work well
 with your hands, the ability to accept criticism and work well under
 pressure.
 - **2017-2018**
 - MANAGER COFFEE SHOP IN MANJIMUP, WA

WORK BAKER AND COFFEE SHOP

- managers oversee all their business's daily operations, including the
 production of baked goods, sales, and personnel management. They
 coordinate between the baking team, the salespeople, and the
 customers while ensuring that quality and safety standards are
 maintained.
 - 2022-PRESENT
 - AQS TANNERY GROUP

AGRICULTURE WORKERS

SKILLS

- Project Management
- **Public Relations**
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking
- HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT AND **REACT WEBSITE**

LANGUAGES

- English (fluent)
- Vietnamese (fluent)

REFERENCE

ALEX DANILOV-LAVERTON, VIC

+6141533153

Manager Coffee Shop In WA

+61434552074

- · used to produce sheepskin leather products and soft wool-lined clothing or coverings, including gloves, hats, slippers, footstools, automotive seat covers, baby and knee rugs and pelts.
 - 2022-PRESENT
 - **FREELANCER**

DEVELOP WEBSITE

- · Develop and maintain strong relationships with partners, agencies, and vendors to support marketing initiatives.
- Monitor and maintain brand consistency across all marketing channels and materials.

ENGINEERING TECHNOLOGISTS

DEVELOP WEBSITE

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/fccfcf42caeea00-4c88-b05f-6d41eae9ad18/responsive-web-design

JAVASCRIPT-ALGORITHMS-AND-**DATA-STRUCTURES**

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/fccfcf42caeea00-4c88-b05f-6d41eae9ad18/javascript-algorithmsand-data-structures-v8

FRONT-END-DEVELOPMENT-**LIBRARIES**

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/fccfcf42caeea00-4c88-b05f-6d41eae9ad18/front-end-developmentlibraries

DATA-**VISUALIZATION** https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/fccfcf42caeea00-4c88-b05f-6d41eae9ad18/data-visualization

INTEREST





